Izzah Amjad



izzahamjad61@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/izzah-amjad-uiuxdesigner



https://behance.net/izzahamjad3

Summary

Hi, I'm a Professional Graphic and UI/UX Designer. I am expert in all services of Graphic Designing. I work with the understanding of the Client and the developers. I love what I do & enjoy learning new things everyday. I can help you to achieve fast turnaround with all your design projects. Feel free to contact me anytime & discuss your design project. Let's get it done!

Experience



BlocTech Solutions Sep 2022 - Present (9 months)

Ul Designer

freelance Feb 2023 - Present (4 months)

Graphic Designer

The YOU Company
Mar 2022 - Jun 2022 (4 months)

Education

Government College University, Faisalabad

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science Oct 2019 - Sep 2023

Superior College

Intermediate, ICS Sep 2017 - Sep 2019

Mian Nazir Hussein Model Secondary School Jaranwala

Matric, Computer Science Mar 2014 - Jul 2016

Licenses & Certifications



û UX/UI Design - Udemy

Skills

Web Design • Mobile Application Design • Stationery Design • User Interface Prototyping • Prototyping • Wireframing • User Flows • Standee Design • User Interface Design • Poster Design